A Finding Aid to the Robert W. White Papers, 1889-2003, bulk 1915-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.whiterobe
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, 1952-2003; Series 3; (Boxes 4-5, OV 10; 1.2 linear feet)
  Project files contain a majority of Robert W. White's solo and group exhibitions and his public and private commissions.
  This subseries is arranged as two subseries:
  3.1: Exhibitions, 1952-2003
  3.2: Commissions, 1922-1997
  - Exhibitions, 1952-2003; 3.1
    Files document some of Robert White's exhibitions; there are extensive files on his shows at Davis Galleries, Graham Gallery, Graham Modern, and the State University of New York at Stony Brook.
    Materials include correspondence; loan agreements, commissions, lists of artwork, sales, notes, and receipts; press releases; artwork; and photographs, including negatives, slides, and a transparency of exhibition installations.
    Also found are Robert White's annotated lists of artwork, receipts, guest lists for an unidentified exhibition, and a miscellaneous exhibition list.
    Files are arranged chronologically by year of exhibition. Exhibitions are also referred to in Series 2: Correspondence, Series 4: Personal Business Records, Series 5: Notes and Writings, Series 7: Printed Material, and Series 10: Photographs.
    - Davis Galleries (Box 4)
      - Letters to Robert White, Primarily Related to the Sale of Artwork, 1957-1968; (8 folders) (Box 4, Folder 60-67)
      - Notes, 1960, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Lists of Artwork Sold, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - List of Drawings, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Heckscher Museum (Box 4)
      - Letters to Robert White, 1962-1983 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - Receipts for Artwork, 1966-1983 (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - Various Receipts, 1979-1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
      - Loan Agreements, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 74)
      - Notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1964, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 76)
      - Loan Agreements Relating to Exhibitions at the Fine Arts Center, 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 77)
      - Loan Agreements Relating to Faculty Art Exhibitions, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 78)
      - Press Release on Faculty Art Exhibition (September 1994) (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Truckman Order Receipts Relating to Faculty Art Exhibitions, 1984-1997 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Lists of Artwork, 1963, undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - Exhibition Brochure, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Transparencies of Visitors to Exhibition, undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Elaine Benson Gallery (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1971, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - Contract Form, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - Exhibition Schedule, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 86)
      - Memorandum regarding Announcements, Posters, and Exhibition Schedule, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Miscellaneous Receipts and Notes, 1972-1985 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Graham Gallery (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1979; (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 89-92)
      - Commission of Medallion for the New School of Social Research, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 93)
      - Statement of Commission Agreement with Robert White, undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
      - Memoranda Relating to Insurance Value for Various Sculptures, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 95)
      - Schedule of Exhibitions for 1978-1979, undated (Box 4, Folder 96)
      - Various Receipts and Notes, 1978-2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
      - Miscellaneous Label, undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Installation Photographs includes Negatives, 1992-2001, undated; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 99-101)
    - Graham Modern (Box 4)
      - Letters to Robert White, Primarily relating to Sale of Artwork, 1980-1990, undated (Box 4, Folder 102)
      - Sales, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 103)
      - Lists of Artwork, circa 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 104)
      - Price List for Bronze and Terra Cotta Figures (1959-1986), circa 1986 (Box 4, Folder 105)
      - Client List, 1987, undated (Box 4, Folder 106)
      - Inventory of Photographs and Slides of Artwork, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 107)
      - Release Forms, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 108)
      - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 109)
      - Layout of Wall Stands and Floor Plan, circa 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Suffolk Museum and Carriage House (Box 5)
      - Loan Agreement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - List of Robert White Artwork for Artists of Suffolk County Exhibit (October 23-November 11, 1983) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Gallery North (Box 5)
      - Agreement, Contract, and Receipts, 1974-1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Art Consignments, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Price Lists, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Boston Athenaeum (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Lists of Artwork included in Exhibition, circa 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Invitation List, circa 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Photographs of Exhibition Space, circa 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hartwick College (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Lists of Artwork (1952-1975), circa 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Price List, circa 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Copy of Sketch of Exhibition Space and Slides, circa 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Artists Choice Museum, Loan Agreements, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Pratt Institute, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - C.W. Post, Long Island University, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Contemporary Realist Gallery, Consignment Memo, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Century Association, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Lists (Box 5)
      - Lists of Artwork including Sale Prices, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Lists of Receipts, 1978-1988 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Lists of Sculpture and Bases with Measurements and Prices, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - List of Artwork for Unidentified Exhibition, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Guest Lists for Unidentified Exhibitions, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Miscellaneous Invitation List, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Commissions, 1922-1997; 3.2
    The subseries documents several commissioned projects, including St. Anthony of Padua at East Northport, New York; The Verrill Medal for the Peabody Museum; Portrait of Mr. and Mrs. Ward Melville for the Long Island Hall of Fame; and General George Pershing Memorial for the American Battles Monuments Commission. Also found are files for White's work for Steuben Glass and the artist's unexecuted design proposal for the John F. Kennedy Memorial at the Massachusetts State Capitol.
    Folders contain correspondence, notes, agreements, invoices, printed material, clippings, photographs, and a transparency.
    Files are arranged in chronological order by year of exhibition. Commissions are also referred to in Series 2: Correspondence, Series 4: Personal Business Records, Series 5: Notes and Writings, Series 7: Printed Material, and Series 10: Photographs.
    - Steuben Glass, 1957-1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - St. Anthony of Padua (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1959; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
      - Agreement between the Modern Art Foundry and Robert White, 1959 (Folder 29)
    - John Oeschlin, Inc., Invoice, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - St. Michael's Church, 1959-1966, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - The Botolph Group, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - The Verrill Medal, Peabody Museum (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1966, undated; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 33-35)
      - Notes, Purchase Order, and Check Statement, 1960, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Metallic Art Company, Acknowledgment of Order, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - John F. Kennedy Memorial (Unexecuted) (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1966; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
      - Robert White's Notes on His Proposed Submission, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Miscellaneous Note, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Various Sketch Designs, circa 1986 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Lists of Semi-Finalists, circa 1987 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Various Printed Material, 1984-1988, undated; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 44-45)
      - Photographs, circa 1961-1986; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 46-47)
    - Harkness House for Ballet Arts, 1964-1966, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Portrait of Mr. and Mrs. Ward Melville, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Monument to Bishop Cranmer, St. James Episcopal Church, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - General George Pershing Memorial (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Agreement between Robert White and the American Battle Monuments Commission (copy; unsigned), undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - Contract Order with Modern Art Foundry, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Cut Plan, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Notes relating to Payment and Payment Vouchers include Snapshots of Model and Base, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Fact Sheet, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Miscellaneous Transmittal Letters and Receipt, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Clippings, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Copies of Reference Photographs of General George Pershing (1917-1919), undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Plan and Elevation for the General George Pershing Memorial, 1979; (See OV 10) (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Various Printed Material, 1922, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Sketch of Plan for the General George Pershing Memorial area, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Portrait of John Swearingen, University of South Carolina (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Expenditure Voucher, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Notes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Clipping, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Invoice for Replacement for Portrait, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Head of Dr. Ackerman, Washington University, 1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Bronze Fountain and Bull for Frank and Patricia Huntington, 1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Oversized Plan and Elevation for the General George Pershing Memorial, 1979 (Box 10)
- Personal Business Records, 1889, 1946-2003; Series 4; (Boxes 5-6; 1.3 linear feet)
  Personal business records include materials pertaining to Robert White's involvement on the Executive Committee of the Augustus Saint-Gaudens Memorial and at National Academy of Design; his teaching appointments at the Parsons School of Design and the State University of New York at Stony Brook; and his dealings with foundries, mainly the Modern Art Foundry and the stone engraver, John Stevens Shop. Also included are scattered files on the Whites' family residence amd property in St. James, New York; price lists for artwork; loan agreements to museums from Robert and Claire White's personal art collection; and printouts listing White's sales, exhibitions, sketchbooks, and sculptures, reliefs, drawings, portraits, commercial commissions, and student work.
  Files contain: correspondence and memoranda; lists and notes; and business-related materials, such as deeds, invoices, receipts, sales of artwork, agreements, elevation plans and surveys, and miscellaneous legal and tax records.
  This series is arranged in chronological order. Personal Business Records can be found in Series 2: Correspondence, Series 3: Project Files, and Series 5: Notes and Writings. work (1942-1993).
  The files are arranged in chronological order.
  - Professional Associations (Box 5)
    - The Augustus Saint-Gaudens Memorial, 1963-1986; (30 folders) (Box 5, Folder 70-99)
    - National Academy of Design, 1980-1992; (8 folders) (Box 5, Folder 100-107)
    - Other Professional Associations, 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Teaching Appointments (Box 5)
    - Parsons School of Design, 1957-1981, undated; (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 109-112)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1971-1986; (5 folders) (Box 5, Folder 113-117)
    - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 1973, 1990, undated; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 118-119)
    - Harbor Country Day School, Art Lecture Series, 1973, 1990, undated (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Foundries and Engraver Files (Box 5)
    - Modern Art Foundry, 1957-1992; (7 folders) (Box 5, Folder 121-127)
    - Joel Meisner and Co., Inc., 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - John Stevens Shop, 1961-1963, 1980; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 129-131)
  - St. James, New York Residence and Property (Box 5)
    - Architectural Rendering of Alteration of Tank for Stanford White (May 3, 1889), 1889 (See 0V 10) (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Tax Levy (1945-1946) (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Elevation Plan by Willard R. Huntington for St. James, New York Residence and Property?, 1953 (See OV 10) (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Indenture and Lease to Robert White, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Invoices and Receipts to Lawrence Grant White, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Mortgage to Robert White, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Certificate of Insurance to Robert White and Lawrence Grant White, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Survey Map of Moriches Road, St. James, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Deeds for Parcels of Land, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Notebook of Receipts and Deficits includes Loose Pages of Notes, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Statements of Bills Paid by Lawrence Grant White for Robert White, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Various Receipts, 1953-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 143-144)
  - Ledger of Expenses and Earnings includes Scattered Receipts and Notes, 1956-1998 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Ledger of Receipts and Deficits includes List of Various Sculptures with Dimensions and Approximate Price List, 1999-2003, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Prices for Artwork Sold, 1957-1960, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cost of Supplies, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Notes Pertaining to Artwork, 1965, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Various Invoices, 1987-1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Loan Agreements to Museums from Robert and Clare White's Personal Art Collection, 1959-1971, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Record of Sales (1946); Catalogs (1949-2001); and Sketchbooks (1950s-1980s, undated), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Record of Reproductions of Robert White's Sculptures, Reliefs, Drawings, Portraits, Commercial Commissions, and Student Work (1942-1993), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Loose Addresses of Business Contacts, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Other Personal Business Files (Box 6)
    - 1040 Tax Filing (Draft) and 1099 Documentation, 1955-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Last Will and Testament and First Codicil of Lawrence Smith Butler, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Building Regulation Form, Head-of-the-Harbor Village, Smithtown, New York, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Memorandum re 1986 Distributions of Interest Income, Springbriar Mortgage, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Notice of Probate for the Estate of Sheila D. Emmet, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Memorandum Agreement to Sell Thomas Dewing Portrait of Ella Emmet, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Letter Agreement with the New York Foundation for the Arts, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Loose Envelopes, 1945-1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Oversized Architectural Rendering of Alteration of Tank for the St. James, New York Residence and Property for Stanford White (May 3, 1889) (Box OV 10)
  - Oversized Elevation Plan by Willard R. Huntington for the St. James, New York Residence and Property? (May 5, 1953) (Box OV 10)
- Notes and Writings, 1915, circa 1946-2002; Series 5; (Boxes 6-7; 0.6 linear feet)
  Notes and writings include Robert White's diaries, artist's statements, notebooks, essays, and lectures. Included are writings by others, mostly reviews of White's work and some writings by Clare White.
  Eleven pocket diaries record White's activities at home, his travels in Europe and Mexico, exhibition openings, and social engagements with family, colleagues, and friends. Notebooks contain: White's drafts of letters, artist's statements, proposals, poems, essays, talks, notes on artwork sold and expenses, a list of the artwork completed for the years 1939-1946, and loose addresses. Two items of interest are Robert White's letter to William Styron discussing the writer's novel, Sophie's Choice and his memorial to his friend and colleague, Fairfield Porter. Found within the notebooks and diaries are sketches by the artist.
  Notes and writings can be also found in Series 4: Personal Business Records.
  Files are arranged in chronological order.
  - Diaries (Box 6)
    - 1983-1984 (2 volumes) (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 1987 (2 volumes) (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - 1988-1989 (2 volumes) (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - 1990-1991 (2 volumes) (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - 1992-1993 (2 volumes) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Artist's Statements, 1993, undated; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
  - Notebooks (Box 6)
    - Circa 1946 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Circa 1948, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Circa 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Circa 1980s, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 29-30)
    - Circa 1986-2000 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - 1990, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Circa late 1990s-2000, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
    - Circa 1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Circa 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - 1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Circa 1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Circa 1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Essays by Robert White (Box 6)
    - "The Casting of the Shaw Monument,", circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - "On Plaster Originals,", circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - "The Future of Art,", circa 1982, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - "The Shining of the Sherman,", circa 1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - "Taste and Tolerance,", 1992 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - "The Artistic Political Interface,", undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Lectures by Robert White (Box 6)
    - Lecture at the Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Preliminary Outline of Proposed Experimental Course in Architectural Ornament, circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Classroom Lectures, circa 1980s; (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 48-51)
    - "On the American Realist Painting and Drawing,", undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - "On the Teaching Philosophy at the National Academy of Design,", undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Notes for a Lecture, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Speech by Robert White at the State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Various Notes by Robert White, undated; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 56-57)
  - Lists of Artwork, 1965, undated; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Writings by Robert White, 1980, undated; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 59-60)
  - Poems by Robert White, circa 1990s-2000; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 61-62)
  - Writings By Others (Box 6)
    - You May Stay, Elisha, Being A Short Play in Praise of the Beauty of Miss Clare Nicolas, circa 1946 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Writings by Colleagues, Critics, and Friends on Robert White, 1963-2002, undated; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 64-65)
    - Art Letter by Valentin Tatransky, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Catalog Review for Robert W. White Retrospective by Paul Werner, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Various Poems by Others, 1915, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Sketchbooks and Sketches, circa 1965-1972; Series 6; (Boxes 7, 9; 0.3 linear feet)
  This series primarily includes Robert White's preliminary studies, in ink, pencil, charcoal, and watercolor of portraits and full-length figures; dancers; animals and armature; and angels and mythological figures. Sketchbooks were titled by the artist. There are also scattered sketches by others.
  Sketches are also found in Series 1: Correspondence, Series 3: Project Files, and Series 4: Personal Business Records.
  - Sketchbooks (Box 7)
    - "Fencers, Dances (Rebekah Harkness), and Young Girl,", circa 1965, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Dancers,", circa 1965, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Cavalcade, Horseman, Dancer, and Life Studies Nudes,", circa 1972, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Dancers and Terra Cotta Portraits of Diggle Helman and Stephanie White,", undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Animals and Armature,", undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Apollo, Hercules, and Arimanthean Boar,", undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Male and Female Nudes,", undated; (See Box 9) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "Female Nudes, Angel, and Horses,", undated; (See Box 9) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Various Sketches, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sketch and Elevation of St. James, New York Residence by Robert White, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Sketches by Robert White, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Sketches by Others, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Oversized Sketchbook, "Life Drawings and Female Nudes", undated (Box 9)
  - Oversized Sketchbook, "Female Nudes, Angel, and Horses,", undated (Box 9)
- Printed Material, 1937-2003; Series 7; (Box 7, 9; 0.5 linear feet)
  This series houses newspaper clippings, reviews,and periodicals; exhibition announcements, catalogs, brochures, and posters; press releases; newsletters; reproductions of artwork; and miscellaneous printed material. Clippings and reviews document Robert White's exhibitions, beginning with his first show at the Stony Brook Museum in 1947. Included are reproductions of White's illustrations for periodicals. Also found are posters of Robert White's exhibitions at the Benson Gallery and the Graham Gallery.
  Other printed material can be found in Series 2: Correspondence, Series 3: Project Files, Series 4: Personal Business Records, and Series 5: Notes and Writings.
  The series is arranged in chronological order.
  - Clippings on Robert White's Work (Box 7)
    - 1945-1955 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 1970-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 1996-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Clippings Related to the Admiral Farragut, 1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Clippings Relating to Family and Friends, 1947-1964, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Periodicals, 1950-1970; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 24-25)
  - Reviews of Robert White's Artwork, 1950-1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Reviews on Artwork by Other Artists, 1985, 1993, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1950-1994, undated; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 28-30)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1948, 1961-2003; (14 folders) (Box 7, Folder 31-44)
  - Exhibition Brochures, circa 1947-1983, undated; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 45-46)
  - Exhibition Posters, Robert White's Exhibition at the Graham Gallery and the Benson Gallery Summer Exhibition, circa 1970-1971; (See Box 9) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Press Releases and Newsletters, 1976-1988, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1940-1994, undated; (See Also Box 9) (Box 7, Folder 49-53)
  - Oversized Exhibition Posters, Robert White's Exhibition at the Graham Gallery and the Benson Gallery Summer Exhibition, circa 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Oversized Miscellaneous Printed Material, Blueprint for Clipper Ship Sea Witch (1933), undated; (See Box 9) (Box 9)
- Audiovisual Material, 1973; Series 8; (Box 7; 1 folder)
  The series contains one item, an audio CD-Disc of Robert White's classroom lecture.
  - Audio CD-Disc of Robert White Classroom Lecture (unidentified venue), Parts 1 and 2, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Artifacts, 1973; Series 9; (Boxes 7; 0.1 linear feet)
  This series contains a few objects found among Robert White's papers: printing blocks feature an image of White's portrait sculpture of his daughter, Stephanie White and a landscape view; and a patch of fabric with an unidentified insignia.